Prey for love.
Frank and Penelope is a thriller, horror, crime film
directed by Sean Patrick Flanery.
A tale of love and violence when a man on his emotional last legs finds
a savior seductively dancing in a run-down strip club.
And a life most certainly headed off a cliff suddenly becomes
redirected - as everything is now worth dying for.
Frank, played by Billy Budinich.
Penelope, played by Caylee Cowan.
Chisos, played by Johnathon Schaech.
Cleve, played by Brian Maillard.
Molly, played by Sydney Scotia.
Sheriff, played by Kevin Dillon.
Frank and Penelope is a 2022 American romantic crime film
written and directed by Sean Patrick Flanery.
The film stars Billy Budinich, Caylee Cowan, Kevin Dillon, Donna D'Errico,
Lin Shaye, Johnathon Schaech, and Sean Patrick Flanery.
The film is a road movie that begins in the city of Austin, Texas traveling
along a deserted stretch of dirt road miles from civilization.
It then takes place in the ghost town of Terlingua, Texas which devolves into chaos and violence after it is discovered
that the proprietor of the motel and diner, Chisos, is a psychotic cannibal along with his sadistic family.
Frank and Penelope suddenly become immersed in a hellish nightmare, on a life and
death journey, where escape is just a heart-pounding breath away.
Frank & Penelope had its world premiere at the Riviera
International Film Festival in Italy on May 14, 2022.
It's also been screened as part of the Cannes Film Festival
market where Fabrication Films acquired film rights.
Frank & Penelope was theatrically released in the United States on June 3, 2022.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.